Guide to the Washington Office on Africa Records
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Resource File - By Topic, Series VIII
  - General / Miscellaneous
    - Media
      - Lists of press contacts (See also: Serie IV: WOA interaction with media), 1988, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 253)
      - Africa News, 1977-1983 (Box 61, Folder 254)
      - Misc. correspondence, reports, 1980-1984 (Box 61, Folder 255)
    - South African propaganda in U.S.
      - Misc. correspondence, reports, 1975-1984 (Box 61, Folder 256-257)
      - Christian League of Southern Africa, 1979, n.d. (Box 61, Folder 258, 258a)
      - Publisher John McGoff, 1975-1983 (Box 61, Folder 259)
      - Images Industries, 1975-1982 (Box 62, Folder 260)
      - Sydney Baron and Co., 1976-1979 (Box 62, Folder 261)
      - Collier, Shannon, Rill, Edwards and Scott, 1975-1980 (Box 62, Folder 262)
      - South Africa and the Clark-Jepsen Iowa Senate campaign, 1978-1979 (Box 62, Folder 263)
      - Paper by Shelly Pitterman, 1977 (Box 66, Folder 5)
    - United States Foreign Policy
      - Law of the Sea Treaty, 1974-1983 (Box 62, Folder 264)
      - Reagan administration policies, 1981-1985 (Box 62, Folder 265)
      - U.S. contributions to United Nations programs concerned with Southern Africa, 1983-1984 (Box 62, Folder 266)
      - Paper on "The Impact of Lobbying on U.S. Foreign Policy Toward South Africa" by William Marsh, 1979 (Box 66, Folder 9)
  - Miscellaneous U.S. Religious Organizations and Churches
    - Catholic Church (Box 62, Folder 2670268)
    - Lutheran groups (Box 62, Folder 269,270)
    - Right wing groups (Box 63, Folder 271)
    - Jerry Falwell - Moral Majority (Box 63, Folder 272)
    - YWCA (Box 63, Folder 273)
    - Miscellaneous church statements and publications (Box 63, Folder 274-278)